ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- The Amalgamated Insurance Fund (CLOFUND) Meeting of the Executive Committee and Meeting of the Investment Committee, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  June 10 and 16.
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (CLOFUND) Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  June 16
- Actuarial Valuation for the Textile Staff Retirement Plan United States Participants, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  July 15. 2 copies.
- Agenda Meeting of the Committee Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  July 15
- Annual Return/ Report of Employee Benefit Plan, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance and Amalgamated Insurance Fund Investment Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, Insurance Fund and Cotton Garment and Allied Industries, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Domestic and International Pension Investment Issues, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Health Care, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Greif Companies [1 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Greif Companies [2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 136, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Health Care, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- Hofstra Russian Program, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- Hosfra University Moscow Program, 1992-1993 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1990-1992 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- International Rescue Committee, Incorporated, 1991-1993 (Box 136, Folder 7)
- General Office Finance, 1992-1993 (Box 136, Folder 8)
- Genesco, 1993-1994 (Box 136, Folder 9)
- Governor's Commission on Competitiveness, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- Greif Companies, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 1)
- Harvard University, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Healthtex, 1992-1994 (Box 137, Folder 3)
- Hertz (Box 137, Folder 4)
- Hillman Hall of Fame and Health Care, 1990-1995 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- Norman Hilton, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  April 17
- Highlander Research and Education Center, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  February 18
- International Affairs Department, 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 8)
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  February 10
- Irish American Labor Coalition, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  October 25 and 27
- Industrial Union Department Labor Policy Institute (Box 137, Folder 11)
- Industrial Union Department Pension and Benefit Committee, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  September 11
- Industrial Union Department Venture Capital Fund, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  May 14
- Industrial Union Department Women Officers (Box 137, Folder 14)
- Industrial Union Department International Trade Committee, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  November 18 and May 3
- Johnson and Johnson, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 16)
- Occupational Safety and Health Committee and Industrial Union Department Committee on Reindustrialization, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  February 25
- Japan, 1991-1992 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  June 28 and December 8
- Jay Mar Ruby, 1989-1991 (Box 137, Folder 19)
- Edward Kennedy, 1991-1993 (Box 137, Folder 20)
- King Center, 1992-1995 (Box 137, Folder 21)
- Kleen Brite Laboratories, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  March 11 and April 1
- Labor Advisory Committee for Trade Negotiations and Trade Policy, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 23)
- Labor Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 137, Folder 24)
- Labor Leadership Newsletter, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  January
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 26)
- Labor Research Association, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 27)
- Labor Unity, 1991-1994 (Box 137, Folder 28)
- Harry Lautman, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  January 19
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Leadership Conference, 1990-1994 (Box 137, Folder 30)
- Lehigh Project (Pennsylvania), 1992 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  January 7
- Letters to the Editor, Articles, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  March 16
- The Martin Luther King, Junior Federal Holiday Commission [1 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Thirtieth Anniversary of the 1963 March on Washington, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 2)
- Martin Luther King Junior, Labor Committee, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  October 19 and December 1
- Martin Luther King Committee Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  February 24
- The King Center, 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 5)
- Twentieth Anniversary Mobilization (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, 1991-1993 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation, 1991-1995 (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Industrial Union Department Nominating Committee, 1992 (Box 139, Folder 2)
- Industrial Union Department Convention, 1991-1992 (Box 139, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union Department Pension and Benefits, 1991-1993 (Box 139, Folder 4)
- Industrial Union Department Financial Statements and Schedules, 1992 (Box 139, Folder 6)
- Industrial Union Department, 1991-1993 (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 139, Folder 8)
- The Martin Luther King, Junior Federal Holiday Commission [2 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 139, Folder 9)
- Jewish Labor Committee Germany Trip, 1977-1978 (Box 140, Folder 1)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  April 12
- Jewish Labor Committee Human Rights Awards, 1972-1978 (Box 140, Folder 3)
- Jewish Labor Committee Labor Law Reforms, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- Jewish Labor Committee Legislature Program, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  April 11
- Jewish Labor Committee: National Commission on Social and Economic Issues, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- Jewish Labor Committee: National Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- National Trade Union Council for Human Rights, 1977-1978 (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Jewish Labor Committee New York, 1976-1978 (Box 140, Folder 9)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Office Committee Meeting, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Printed Matter, 1970-1980 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- Jewish Labor Committee Full Employment, 1976-1978 (Box 140, Folder 12)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Resolutions Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 140, Folder 13)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Speeches, 1975-1978 (Box 140, Folder 14)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Western Regional Conference, 1977-1979 (Box 140, Folder 15)
- National Committee for Labor Israel: General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 16)
- National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council Speeches, 1977 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  January 27
- "Old Timers" Jacob Sheinkman, 1973-1976 (Box 140, Folder 18)
- Presidents Conference, 1976-1979 (Box 140, Folder 19)
- Jewish Labor Committee Action, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Jewish Labor Committee [1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Committees and Commissions, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  April 5
- Jewish Labor Committee: Contributions, 1974-1978 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Convention, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  Hebrew
- Jewish Labor Committee: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Jewish Labor Committee [2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Executive Staff Retirement Plan, 1969-1972 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Employees Retirement Plan (Actual Plan), 1970 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  July 8
- Jewish Labor Committee Employees Retirement Plan, 1972-1976 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Executive Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Jewish Labor Committee: Field Staff Conference, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  November 19-20
- Jewish Labor Committee: George Meany Journal [1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 141, Folder 13)
- Jewish Labor Committee: George Meany Journal [2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 141, Folder 14)
- Local 169, 1991-1995 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Ernesto Jofre Member Local 169 Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Joseph and Feiss, 1990-1993 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Tennessee and Kentucky Office, 1992-1995 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Texas Joint Board, 1993 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  July 7
- Toronto Joint Board Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1991-1995 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Western New York Joint Board, 1992-1993 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- Western Regional Joint Board, 1992-1994 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, 1994-1995 (Box 142, Folder 9)
- Local 1733, 1993-1994 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1992 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  February 7
- South Regional Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1991-1994 (Box 142, Folder 13)
- Quebec Joint Board, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  June 5 and 19
- Rochester Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Joint Board, 1990-1992 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- South Carolina Costal Joint Board, 1993-1995 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Joint Board North Alabama, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Ontario Joint Council, 1993-1995 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1990-1995 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 9)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- Neckwear Joint Board, 1991-1994 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- New England Regional Joint Board, 1991-1994 (Box 143, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 13)
- New York and New Jersey Joint Board, 1990-1995 (Box 143, Folder 14)
- El Paso Joint Board, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  October 22 and November 7
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 16)
- Headwear and Allied Workers, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 17)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 18)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 19)
- Mid Atlantic Joint Board, 1990-1995 (Box 143, Folder 20)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 21)
- California Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 22)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 23)
- Central Ontario Regional Office, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  October 17
- Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 25)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1991-1993 (Box 143, Folder 26)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, 1990-1995 (Box 143, Folder 27)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 28)
- Florida Joint Board, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 29)
  April 27
- Miscellaneous Joint Board, 1991-1995 (Box 143, Folder 30)
- Arkansas Joint Board, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 31)
- Amalgamated Services, 1991-1994 (Box 143, Folder 32)
- Baltimore Joint Board, 1992-1994 (Box 143, Folder 33)
- Georgia Tennessee Alabama Joint Board, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 34)
  March 12
- Organizing Department [1 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Organizing Department [2 of 2], 1994 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Szold and Brandwen, 1991-1994 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Legislative Department, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Legislative and Political Action Manual, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  March 26-31
- New York State Politics, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  ..
- New York State Business Venture Partnership, 1991-1993 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- Rothschild Ventures, 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- New York Historical Society Board of Trustees, 1992-1995 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- New York Historical Society, 1992-1995 (Box 144, Folder 10)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  December 20
- Levi Strauss and Company, 1992 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Letters to the Editor and Articles, 1991-1993 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Legislative and Political Education Department, 1991-1993 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Moynihan Bill, 1993 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- Arthur Loevy, 1991-1992 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- Salant Corporation, 1991-1993 (Box 145, Folder 6)
- Mexico Free Trade Agreement, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 7)
- London Fog, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Londontown Corporation, 1993-1994 (Box 146, Folder 2)
- Liz Clairborne Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Made in the United States of America, 1992-1993 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Mailgrams, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Monroe Manufacturing, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  November 22
- Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  February 8
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- National Black Caucus of State Legislators, 1991-1992 (Box 146, Folder 9)
- National Clothing Agreement, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- National Clothing Industry Labor Management Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 146, Folder 11)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1993-1995 (Box 146, Folder 12)
- National Center for the Workplace, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 13)
- Navaco Industries Incorporated, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  January 12
- New York Times, 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 15)
- North America Integration Panel, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 16)
  July 1 and November 5
- New York City Productivity Advisory Council, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 17)
- Local 169 [1 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 147, Folder 1)
- Local 169 [2 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 147, Folder 2)
- The United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1992-1993 (Box 147, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank [1 of 5], 1991-1992 (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank [2 of 5], 1992 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank [3 of 5], 1993 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank [4 of 5], 1990-1991 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank [5 of 5], 1994 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Salant Corporation, 1991-1994 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Middle East Crisis, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Mission Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1991-1993 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Education Fund Incorporated, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- National Labor Committee Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- National Leadership Coalition for Health Care Reform, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- National Committee for Labor Israel, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- National Labor Committee El Salvador, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 8)
- National Planning Association [1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 9)
- National Planning Association [2 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- New York Historical Society, 1991-1993 (Box 149, Folder 11)
- Committee on New American Realities, 1991-1993 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Americans for Democratic Action, 1974-1989 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- American Jewish Congress, 1981-1990 (Box 150, Folder 3)
- Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), 1990-1993 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- American Open University, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Teachers, 1974-1987 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1991 (Box 150, Folder 7)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- American Made Goods (Box 150, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Attendance, 1993 (Box 150, Folder 10)
- Auto Industry, 1988 (Box 150, Folder 11)
- Automation, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  April 26
- Organizing Tactics and Strategies Bag and Packaging Industry, 1991 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  February 26
- Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 150, Folder 14)
- Berlin, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 15)
- The Master Association News, 1993 (Box 150, Folder 16)
- Barbados (Box 150, Folder 17)
- Balanced Budget Constitutional Amendment, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  June 8-9
- The Bildisco Decision, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 19)
- Carol Bellamy Campaign, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 20)
  July 3 and 17
- Fourteenth World Congress of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1988 (Box 150, Folder 21)
  March 14-18
- Australia, 1987-1988 (Box 150, Folder 22)
- Refugee Services, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 23)
- Asian American Free Labor Institute, 1980-1993 (Box 150, Folder 24)
- Aspen Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 150, Folder 25)
- Athletic Uniforms, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 26)
- Associate Membership Program, 1987-1989 (Box 150, Folder 27)
- Apprenticeship, 1973 (Box 150, Folder 28)
- Arab Countries, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 29)
- Arbitration, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 30)
- Arthritis Foundation, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 31)
  August 22 and September 2
- Dorothy File, 1989 (Box 150, Folder 32)
- Apparel Industry, 1989-1991 (Box 150, Folder 33)
- Ruth Antoniades, 1973-1974 (Box 150, Folder 34)
- American Society of Professional and Executive Women, 1981 (Box 150, Folder 35)
- Amalgamated Political Education Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 36)
- Amnesty (Box 150, Folder 37)
- American Work Force (Box 150, Folder 38)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1974-1991 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization Executive Council, 1981-1987 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- The United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1980-1984 (Box 151, Folder 3)
- Campaign for America's Future, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- The Future of Big Business Day (Box 151, Folder 5)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Incorporated, 1983-1984 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit (Box 151, Folder 7)
- Constitutional Limits on Federal Spending and Deficits (Box 151, Folder 8)
- The Reagan Recession, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 9)
- Vice President Miller, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 10)
- John Harling's Labor Letter, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 11)
- Background Concepts Labor as a Capital Provider, 1986 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  February 19
- Mailgrams, 1980-1988 (Box 151, Folder 13)
- Texas, 1990 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  September 27
- American Civil Liberties Union, 1978-1991 (Box 151, Folder 15)
- News Articles, 1973-1984 (Box 151, Folder 16)
- Reaganomics: A Profile of Failure, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 17)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization Mailing List Directory, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 18)
- An Ordinance of the City of Minneapolis, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 19)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1981-1992 (Box 151, Folder 20)
- Graphic Communications International Union, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union and American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  May 18
- Reports on the Workshops at the 1982 American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization Regional Conferences (Box 151, Folder 23)
  March 15- May 22
- Summary and Report of the Maritime Trades Department, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 24)
- Membership Handbook (Box 151, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous (Box 151, Folder 26)
- Facts for Bargaining: Clothing, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 1)
- Staff Retirement Fund Plan Folder A, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 2)
- Office, Clerical and Miscellaneous Employees Retirement Plan Folder B, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 3)
- Staff Health Benefits Plan Folder C (Box 152, Folder 4)
- Office, Clerical and Miscellaneous Employees Health Benefits Plan (Box 152, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Bargaining Unit Directory, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 6)
- Contracts, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 7)
- Insurance, 1995 (Box 152, Folder 8)
- Facts for Bargaining: Clothing, 1995 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- Cotton Negotiations, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 10)
- The Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Box 152, Folder 11)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume 1, 1995 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  June 22-30
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume 2, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 13)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume 3, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 14)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume 4, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 15)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume 5, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 16)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union General Office Financial Statements, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 17)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America Negotiations [1 of 2], 1990 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Merger Information Volume [2 of 2], 1990 (Box 153, Folder 2)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 4)
- Office, Clerical and Miscellaneous Employees Benefits (Box 153, Folder 5)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Staff Benefits (Box 153, Folder 6)
- Piedmont Airlines, 1986-1991 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Joel Ax Pending, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 2)
- Ron Blackwell Pending, 1991-1994 (Box 154, Folder 3)
- Clay Ola Brown Pending, 1990-1992 (Box 154, Folder 4)
- Kilmer Caban Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 154, Folder 5)
- Caprio Pending, 1991-1994 (Box 154, Folder 6)
- Ed Clark Pending, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 7)
- Alan Cohen Pending, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 8)
- Bruce Dunton Pending, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 9)
- Bernie Ferster Pending, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 10)
- Mark Fleischman Pending, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 11)
- Eric Frumin Pending, 1991-1993 (Box 154, Folder 12)
- John Fox, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  December 14
- Arthur Gundersheim, 1990-1994 (Box 154, Folder 14)
- Nick Hambas Pending, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 15)
- John Hudson Pending, 1992-1994 (Box 154, Folder 16)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 17)
- Charlie Kernaghan, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 18)
- Arthur Loevy Pending, 1991-1993 (Box 154, Folder 19)
- National Labor Committee Pending File, 1993 (Box 154, Folder 20)
- Jo-Ann Mort Pending, 1990-1993 (Box 154, Folder 21)
- Frank Nicholas Pending, 1990-1993 (Box 154, Folder 22)
- Bill Patterson Pending, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 23)
- Bruce Raynor Pending, 1991-1993 (Box 155, Folder 1)
- Harvey Sigelbaum, 1990-1994 (Box 155, Folder 2)
- Joan Suarez Pending, 1991-1993 (Box 155, Folder 3)
- Liz Smith Pending, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  August 17
- Tom Thompson Pending, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 5)
- Nick Unger Pending, 1990-1993 (Box 155, Folder 6)
- Jim Walraven Pending, 1990-1994 (Box 155, Folder 7)
- Steve Weingarten Pending, 1993-1994 (Box 155, Folder 8)
- Al Wertheim Pending, 1991-1994 (Box 155, Folder 9)
- Ken Wray Pending, 1990 (Box 155, Folder 10)
- Mike Zucker Pending, 1990-1993 (Box 155, Folder 11)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [1 of 5], 1989-1991 (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [2 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 156, Folder 2)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [3 of 5], 1986-1987 (Box 156, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [4 of 5], 1989 (Box 156, Folder 4)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [5 of 5], 1987-1988 (Box 156, Folder 5)
- Sheinkman, Betty and Jack Personal Inventory, 1969-1984 (Box 156, Folder 6)
- West 76th Street Block Association, 1989 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- Photo, Cards, News Clipping, 1990-1991 (Box 156, Folder 8)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File, 1990-1992 (Box 157, Folder 1)
- Russian Relatives, 1988-1990 (Box 157, Folder 2)
- Insurance Claims, 1988 (Box 157, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [1 of 5], 1993-1994 (Box 158, Folder 1)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [2 of 5], 1993 (Box 158, Folder 2)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [3 of 5], 1992 (Box 158, Folder 3)
- Jack Sheinkman Personal File [4 of 5], 1992 (Box 158, Folder 4)
- Princeton, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 1)
- Productivity Advisory Council, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  May 26
- The Productivity Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 159, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico Legal Defense and Education, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  November 8
- Per Capita, 1991-1994 (Box 159, Folder 5)
- Parent Action, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 6)
- Phillips Van Heusen Corporation, 1993-1995 (Box 159, Folder 7)
- Pietrafesa Corporation, 1992-1995 (Box 159, Folder 8)
- Palm Beach Incorporated, 1990-1995 (Box 159, Folder 9)
- Operations Department (Dale Marshall), 1991-1994 (Box 159, Folder 10)
- Occupational Health and Safety Forum, 1991-1995 (Box 159, Folder 11)
- Occupational Health Foundation, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 12)
- Asa Philip Randolph, 1991-1994 (Box 159, Folder 13)